It's good! It'll be better to finish it!
Can the dream be fulfill after all?
All the dreams can be fulfilled.
To fulfill that
by the unimaginable magic bag.
I wanna fly in the sky freely.
That's carangid mosquito hawk.
Ah...l like Doraemon best.
Play the doll!
Hurry up, Nobita
Sorry...
I looked for the baseball just now.
All have assembled.
Hey, wait, Nobita!
Come here, please! Please do me a favor!
We're busy now. We're busy now.
You, play with Mimi!
Brother, play with me!
I took it from my home.
Ah? Play the doll'?
Because we're boys! Yeah...
It's shameful! Don't play with her!
Play with her!
Well,
Brother, I've lay down!
Bring the doll here!
Here, take the doll!
If others see we're playing the doll,
it'll be troublesome.
Hey, Nobita! Haven't you started?
It'll be bad if found by him.
Why are you hiding there? Let you be!
Come into the house! Hurry up!
Okay! Play well with the doll!
It's funny! I'll show you all!
It's bad! Something bad happens!
Why don't you play with her?
But...
He isn't here! Where is he?
I really want to see their looks
while they're playing doll!
Nobita, come out now!
How long will you want us to wait?
No way!
Oh, yeah, use that!
Mimi, bring the doll here!
It's this...
What's that?
A robot assembled by the frameworks!
Put this in the doll,
then the doll will move automatically.
It can play by itself!
Wow, the doll can move by itself!
He hasn't appeared yet!
Tell me if he comes out!
Hi, everyone! Sorry to
keep you waiting for so long.
It's different as you said.
Wouldn't you like to
keep playing the doll?
Nonsense! How will I play the doll?
Well, come to have the meal.
Please don't be so rude!
I can't play with you
if you don't cherish us.
Why?
Because we can move automatically.
We're not props for others to play.
First, we have no house,
and no bed and wardrobe.
And we have no table and no TV.
We have nothing at all!
Please cast about for it!
So everyone, assemble!
Let's go to find lung.
Wait!
Brother, the doll want to have a house!
They even said they wanted to
have bed, TV and table!
They're only dolls! How dare to say that
We'll do something! Don't cry!
Lend it to me for a while!
What! Why do you want to borrow that?
I'll give it back to you!
Just lend me for a while! That's okay!
Are these enough? Nobita, you're funny!
It's not used by me!
Okay, so you don't need to complain!
Play together in peace!
It's my first time to play in this way!
All are set! So beautiful!
So we can have the meal now.
You, have something! Okay!
May I join to play with you? Please!
It's time to have the meal now.
Play with me after you're full up, okay?
But it's already night!
You'd better go to sleep!
It's so boring!
It's already morning now!
So let's drive to outside!
Please play with me!
Well, I may play the doll with you!
You're the dolls!
Go to find durable dolls of high quality
We're off!
Hey, wait...
Let me take it... Stand back...
and again stand back
It's too much! Here... No, it's there...
It's there, no...
It's only by a hair!
Here, the ball! Brother, are you painful
It's flesh wound!
It's a piece of cake to a boy!
Ouch...
Brother, come here! You'll go back?
Nobita, what's up to you?
Take a turn over,
I'll be right here at once.
Does it matter?
Stop! You can't do that!
What's going on... That is...
Mom will apply a remedy for you now!
You must be good!
So good you are...
I hate to be treated as a doll.
Time Machine
Shizuka
Nobody answers! Isn't she at home?
Mom dislike those who tell lies.
But I really don't know about it.
Then how will the inkbottle be broke?
It won't turn over itself!
And now only you are at home!
Mom, you did go too far!
I've told you I know nothing about it.
Oh, just apologize faithfully!
But I really didn't do that.
Shizuka will never tell lies.
I'll help her to find the goal bird
and prove her innocency.
Well, let me back to an hour ago.
The inkbottle is still undamaged!
And someone must turn over
the inkbottle during this period!
What's the matter?
I've forgotten some important files.
That's it!
Shizuka's papa is the gaol bird!
Why don't you apologize faithfully?
But I actually don't know that.
Shizuka isn't the gaol bird!
Nobita
Shizuka, make a call to your papa's
company for him!
Call papa now!
Holla, oh, it's you, Shizuka!
What? I did go home just now.
Didn't you turn the inkbottle over?
Inkbottle? As you said that, I feel
as if I've knocked about something.
Absolutely, papa is the gaol bird.
Because I'm in a hurry. I'm sorry...
Thank you! You've done me a big favor!
But how would you know that?
Judge by logic, such as Formosi did!
So that's what it is! What...
Nobita is a great detective!
Nobita, you're great!
What magic did you exert?
Or were you standing aside and watching?
I can't believe!
No magic and no tricks!
It doesn't matter that you won't believe
Anyway, you can ask me for help
if you have some trouble.
In my dictionary, you can't
find the word ' Impossible'!
Whatever it is, I will accomplish it!
And how is the next?
You're using the Time Machine, are you?
Sure enough! Stop!
Why?
Anyway, I just use it to do goods!
It's no matter!
No! Because...
if you use Time Machine to play
detective games,
something terrible will happen.
Terrible things? Why?
I know, it won't work to scare me!
That things won't happen!
I'm serious, Nobita! Leave aside...
Nobita
It's Gian!
Nobita, bumped someone and escaped!
Bumped someone and escaped?
My dad was banged up by the car and
now he's sent to the hospital to cure.
I hate the criminal!
Nobita, please help to find out the car!
I will never forgive him!
Nobita! Ouch... what're you doing?
Thank you!
You're genuine good friends of mine!
You're right! Please let go off me...
Sorry...
I know. Leave it to me.
I'll go to search immediately.
QR
m“!
Nobita, please don't do that.
Doraemon, what do you mean of
asking not to do that?
No, I do not mean that.
Shut up!
You'd be able to see the spot of
the accident from here.
He's coming! He's Gian's dad!
The car is driving from here.
It's right time.
Even the car no. can be took clearly.
This can be the proof.
As long as we investigate the host of
the car, we'll know who offended at once
But is it good to do that?
If I could reach the spot
before the accident happened,
maybe I could prevent it.
So Gian and others won't feel so sad.
What are you talking to yourself?
Yeah, absolutely we should do that.
Nobita...
didn't
One minute before the accident happened,
Gian's papa came over!
He didn't know his fortune.
The car drove in high speed
and it almost...
Oh, no! Don't come over!
Great! I've prevent the accident.
What! You actually did that!
So I've told you not to do that.
Now you've put a foot wrong.
But, Gian's papa is saved.
It's not allowed to use the Time Machine
to change the past at random.
And even if you've changed the fact,
someone will be caught as a whipping boy
On the contrary, if you were the one
who suffered the accident...
What! How comes? You scare me again.
I don't believe that. How could it be so
Isn't this Gian?
Hey, Nobita! Why did you push over my dad
Because you made me
lose my important present, the flilfifi!
Wait...
But so he escaped from
suffering the accident.
What nonsense are you saying?
You guy!
Hey, Gian, stop!
Why do I have to face this situation?
You're so stupid!
Annoying! I won't do that any more.
Great!
It's good that you didn't go too far!
Adventurous Magic Restored Stick!
Piss of me! Only one minute left!
Great! Doraemon isn't here! It's
the last bowl of the instant noodles.
It's still 10 seconds left!
9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3...
Hey, Nobita! Yes!
Come here! Be quick!
He asked me to go there soon...
Because Gian asked you to come here
soon...
It's really troublesome.
You're too slow!
What's the matter? Geez!
The instant noodles will be too soft.
Hi, everyone!
Everybody here? Well, you look...
Till now,
nobody could climb up this tree!
Finally I did climb up the tree!
Great! It's historical!
Is it? Yeah!
Everyone, applause for Gian's courage
and venture!
Congratulation!
What?
Call everyone here expressly
is only for this!
Oh, that guy...
So... Nobita, climb up the tree to show me!
I don't mean that.
Well...now climb up the tree!
I'll climb later.
Now I'm cocking the instant noodles.
Ok, come back here after you're full up!
I won't forgive you if you escape.
I see...
I've said too much!
I couldn't climb up to there at all.
Geez!
Really troublesome! Where is Mechanical
Cat?
The noodles are too soft!
Doraemon! What's the matter?
The case is...
What! It's alright only if
I climb up the tree to show him.
It's easy to do!
Adventurous Magic Restored Stick!
Do you know what's Magic Restored Stick?
It's used by the original residents
of Australia.
Yeah, it's a weapon that will
fly back as being throw out.
Rs theory is same as that.
First, because it's the 1st time, you'd
better enactment the time within 1 sec.
Put this in your bag! And then enactment
the place where you'll control.
Then select here is okay!
Instant horrible feeling!
How do you feel?
I won't climb up again. I thought
I would have fallen down to death.
This machine is made for you
to experience such feeling.
You'll experience the venture
if you climb up.
I'll climb! I must climb up the tree!
Well, that's the top of the tree, right?
Yeah, in order to let Gian watch clearly,
let's enactment within 30 seconds.
It'll begin!
Oh, so high! We'll see stars!
Hey, Gian! What's going on?
Nobody is here!
You look! My hands are almost numb!
So dangerous! I expressly climbed up!
But nobody is there!
Gian, where is you? Hey, you, help me
to find!
Okay! Maybe he's at home!
He's having the delicious snack
leisurely!
Well, let's enactment within 1 second!
C'mon!
Is it okay? Okay!
Strange! When did I eat off it?
You look, I take him back.
Don't use it to do strange things.
From now on,
I'd like to control by myself!
Well, the left of the button stands for
the direction of Northsouth, Westeast!
And next it's the height.
Then press the key to begin.
I know.
Let's go to the zoo to have a look.
Yeah, let's enjoy
the horrible 20 seconds there.
Everybody is frightened.
20 seconds! It's too long!
It's horrible!
But it's interesting that I can't stop!
Now let's enactment within 1 second and
go different place to have a look.
What's that?
How is it...
Really interesting! Hey, Nobita,
I'm here to welcome you.
He's coming!
I'll put the Magic Restored Stick into
the bag and go under the tree directly.
Count the time and press the button!
Sorry to keep you waiting for so long!
I'll climb up the tree quickly
as the appointment.
Very quickly! Let's go!
I heard a loud voice just now!
What's happened?
Nobody is here!
Strange, what machine is it?
Hey, what's going on? Climb up quickly!
Don't be dilatorily!
Doraemon, what're you doing?
Hurry to press the button!
Well? You were so confident just now.
Didn't you put on an act?
So beautiful seascape!
What do the button control?
What're you waiting? Hurry up to climb...
He's missing.
Help...
So strange! He were here just now!
Yes.
I'm taking the big risk! Am I great?
Magic Replaced Stick
I'm back!
Oh, no! Oh, no! My bell is lost.
Bell?
Yeah, that's important to me!
Doraemon is always a storm in a
teacup! Geez!
The bell is almost broken.
It doesn't matter if it's lost.
How long will you intend to
let me get rattled?
Because that's the most important
bell to me! You listen!
Voice from the ceiling!
It must be snapped by the rat.
Then take it back!
Yeah, you're afraid of rat! Ah?
Want me to take it back for you?
I'm not able to climb up to the ceiling!
No way! We have to use that.
Magic Replaced Stick
Take hold of the other side of the stick
We've exchanged our bodies!
So you won't be afraid!
Because it's not your own body.
You're right!
So I'll go to take it for you!
So please!
I find it! Thank you!
This is the gaol bird!
R...Rat!
Why did you bring rats here?
I'm afraid of rats.
The rat isn't here now.
Exchange our bodies back quickly!
Exchange back!
Lend that to me for a while.
This is not for you to play.
Don't you forget that
I've helped you find the bell?
Let you be!
Great!
Let me exchange bodies
with others to help them.
Shizuka, what's wrong with you?
Nobita
I don't want to go home! Why?
The new fraulein is irksome!
He's coming! So irksome!
Well, I'll go back replace Shizuka!
Can you?
Of course!
Here, touch this!
Oh, it's annoying that
I've changed to be so!
How would it be annoying?
Let's go to your home! Let's go!
Hey, wait!
Please don't go too far!
I know. You just stay aside.
Where did you go?
Sensei has been waiting for you so long.
I'm sorry! Because Shizuka shall study
now.
Oh, here comes you!
I've waiting for you so long.
You look more beautiful, Shizuka!
Come here quickly...
It won't work to say that to Shizuka!
Shizuka is mine...
I'm Shizuka! Nice to meet you, Sensei!
So let's review the old lessons first!
Let's begin from the Ex 4!
Such problem will be easy to Shizuka!
Count? ls it this problem? And right now
Clever child like Shizuka
doesn't need to teach at all.
She can count it out quickly.
Show me if you've counted it out!
None of the problems has
been counted out yet!
Never mind! I'm slow because
I want to make right answers.
Be serious in study is what I like
Shizuka.
Isn't Nobita having his lessons seriously?
Finished? It's good that you did it! If
it were Shizuka, she's sure to do right.
All are wrong!
So you're worthy to being taught.
If you know that at the beginning,
then sensei is needless!
You're always praising.
I'm a little tired!
Would you like to have a rest?
Great!
Sometimes we need to adjust our moods.
This suggestion is too great!
I'm used to take a nap at noon.
I won't do such impolite things.
Don't lie down to sleep!
Then have a look at the cartoon!
Don't cross your legs! Poke your nose
into everything! You're boresome!
What're you doing? Don't bother us!
We're studying.
I've driven him away.
That strange kid! You'd better
not to make friends with him.
Strange? What do you mean? What strange'
You did say I was strange.
Sorry, maybe I irritated you!
I apologize!
Yeah, I longed for sending present
to you long before.
Present? Really? Did you?
Of course I did!
Come on tell me! What do you want?
So I'd like to have a peashooter
and a telecopter
and... what I want most is video recorders
And what I most want to have is...
Wait! Let's go to buy! Wait...
Haven't you finished your study?
Help! Wait...
What's it after all?
You've appointed it with me!
Buy it to me soon...
Oh, my Shizuka! She is...
No... I won't...
Shizuka, hurry to exchange your body
back! Please!
No... Because it's shameful!
I don't dare to exchange back with you.
Please don't say so, Shizuka! Hey,
Shizuka...
Formosi Prop
Nobita, you're so slow!
You haven't been back from school.
Mom is in a passion!
He doesn't know that.
Oh, it's Doraemon!
Be careful while walking on the road!
Ouch...
What are you looking? You're so charmed!
Good question!
Formosi
will do that.
According to the clue, the mysterious
case will be solved promptly
So great!
That is, it's important to
take an observation point for point.
And we'd think Of it...
Nobita, where's your schoolbag?
Where's your schoolbag?
Geez!
Where did you lay it? Let's deduce...
It's in Shizuka's home! Why?
Because after school,
I went to Shizuka's home to play.
It's not ratiocination at all.
What're you doing after all?
How are they? It's nothing to do with us
Geez!
You always leave it about here
and there, so it's lost.
I've laid it on the desk.
How would I lost such important things!
Great! Something happened!
Something like diamond is lost.
I'll exercise the Ratiocination of
Formosi to solve this event.
Shizuka will change her attitude!
She'll hold me in respect!
It's impossible!
I think so!
So, Doraemon, what good prop do
you have?
Such as something that can
help us to be famous detectives.
Let you be!
Formosi Prop
It seems you're troubled about something
Let me help you to solve the problem.
What?
As long as I'm here, you don't need
to worry. I can solve all the problems.
Oh, here's the spot of the case!
It's in a mess!
It's my mom and my wrong.
Don't say anything!
I'll deal with all of it!
Clue zoom out!
I can see nothing!
Of course you can't! You can only
see something related to the case.
I saw nothing at all.
The criminal didn't leave any clues!
The window is locked!
Shizuka, have you been in the room?
No, I went out for about 30 minutes,
for my friend called me.
Because we have a long talk,
you went back home, though
you were intend to come to play.
Oh, at that time!
My mom was blithering,
so I rejected to stay playing
and go back home.
But I've gone home already,
so it doesn't matter.
Let's play breezily!
What game is it better to play?
What rubbish are you talking?
Yeah!
So it's easy!
As long as you dive your hat,
you'll be sober-faceted!
What! Actually it's a simple case!
The case happened within 30 minutes
while Shizuka wasn't here.
There's only one who comes
and goes during this period.
So I'm the criminal but not others!
Look, what you made me say!
Not me! Shizuka, please believe me!
It's not me...
No need to explain! Obviously it's you!
Try this!
Gen Stick
The way that the stick leans is the way
that the criminal ran away.
That is, the criminal has
gone away towards here!
It's a trick...
You can't believe that!
Shizuka, please, please believe me!
Please look at my eyes! Do I look like
the man who'll steal the diamond?
Who said I lost the diamond?
What I lost is Formosi memoir
that I lent from the library.
You must help me to find it!
Yeah, so it is!
As I began to read the book
on the desk at my option,
I found it interesting!
So I read it on my way home.
And then I meet you here.
And we have been talking about the book!
When I was home,
I found the book not in my hands.
You still wouldn't like to admit?
But we really don't know that.
Oh, you're still arguing about it!
What's the matter?
Doraemon, help us!
You, listen to me!
When I was trimming the flowers,
suddenly something hit my head!
As I ran out, I saw these two!
We just passed by!
So I have to use this means!
Pipe of Hitting the nail! The bled will
bust up if it meets the criminal's head
Oh, it's you!
You've mistaken! Not me... You've mistaken
What's it after all?
Yeah!
I found it!
Nobita is really a genius!
Next time I lost something,
I'm sure to ask you for help.
But I no more dare do that!
Transform Camera
So annoying! How comes so?
Ouch...
I'm full of mud!
It doesn't matter to soaked!
Nobita, it's not good to your health!
I'm back!
Papa, look at this!
Wait a minute!
Please...look at it!
I'm busy now!
Wait a minute...wait a minute...
Just a moment... Papa! Don't
you think this dresses is beautiful?
Yeah, it is! But I have no money now.
Let's buy it next time.
Nobita, you did dirty the shirt!
You had it on just now!
You'd think for mom!
The weather isn't so nice too!
Take off the dress and have another on!
If you dirty it again,
you'll have no dress to wear!
You're dirty from head to toe! Come in!
Come into the bathroom to take a bath!
I know! I'll take a bath after
I have the clean dress on!
You vented on me
since you can't buy that dress!
It's unfair!
Nobita, what's wrong with you?
I'm alright!
Oh, bad! I was blamed just now.
Only giving you dress to change is okay?
Yeah!
Transform Camera
How to use that?
What dresses would Nobita like to have on
Ah...this...
It should be superman's dress!
I want to have Space dress too!
Oh, you have a head full of bees!
Always you've some odd ideas!
It seems a little different!
Hurry to draw it! That's okay!
Be happy! How about
the sets of two lines' buttons?
Sets of two lines' buttons? So cool!
Take this picture in the camera
and take the lens aim at you.
Direct the dresses against yourself!
Then press the shutter!
So great!
How could you do that?
It's nothing! The theory is very simple!
You can do it only if you
think of the game of lining bricks.
We can combine the bricks
into different shape, right?
This is same as mat.
We combined scattered dress
numerators into the camera.
Any design is okay?
Yeah, any design is okay!
Lend it to me for using!
Do you have any good ideas?
Doraemon's dresses
Isn't this the dresses
for Monkey Ringside?
They fit you very much!
Yeah, we'd send a present to mom!
Is it this magazine?
The dresses that mom likes are on it!
I found! It's this!
What?
What's going on, mom?
You went directly to tailoring
without talking over with me.
Strange!
This is a present I send for you!
I'm going to tailor a good dress
for others.
Don't be high-blown!
Blackcat, sometimes you wish your
hairs' color will be different, will you
Wait for me!
Let me turn your hairs into the color
which other cats will be jealous.
It's Sensei!
I'll give a new dress to sensei
as a present!
This one is not bad! Sensei will
be younger if she have this on!
Good grief!
Failed this time...
ls that boring? Yes...
You'd have they two wore better clothes!
More lovely ones!
What's it after all?
Strange! Well...
You look funny!
When did you begin to dress so?
You look like a fool!
You're too much...too much!
Is that done by Nobita?
You did it, right?
Oh, I'm found!
Stay here, Nobita!
Don't run away, Nobita!
You dare let us in such dresses!
Wait and see!
We'll teach you a good lesson!
Please forgive me,
I won't do that next time!
Please forgive me!
A girl shouldn't do rough stuff!
What? Are you talking about me?
I'd better run away!
What! The camera was taken away!
I'm sorry!
Let you be!
You must be elated!
This camera will help me
fulfill my dream!
What's your dream?
I feel shy and don't know what to say.
This is for you!
What's this?
It's blueprint!
I want to be a pattern maker!
Now I'm studying in it.
Really?
And to be honest,
my real dream is to be a mannequin.
Mannequin?
I'll take advantage of
my strapping body of man!
What a great dream it is!
Yeah, let's hold a habili show!
Good...
Now we'll hold a peculiar habili show!
So you can change the dress in rapid
succession as you're on the stage.
Great...
Are you ready?
OK!
I've already stored lots of
blueprints in the camera.
So let's begin!
It's shameful!
It's not my fault!
Don't run, you bastard!
How did you make him out of dresses?
I drew off the blueprint.
It's brain in the camera.
Healthful entremets!
Delicious.
May I get some more?
No.
But today is our holiday.
It is bad for your body if you drink
more.
I don't think it is delicious.
Why did you also say it like this?
If you agree let me drink more
my body will be good.
And I will go to work tomorrow
spiritedly.
Tomorrow is holiday, I needn't go to
work.
Dad like drink best.
But he is poor, mama doesn't agree.
Because his salary is not high.
So I have a way
I could let him drink racily
Come here...
What?
Tomorrow is dad's birthday.
Then?
I have deposited some money furtively.
This money is only be enough
to buy a bottle of liquor.
Good, I have been moved.
Your words make me remember
a filial son's story.
Long long ago, China has a
younger who worked hard.
That younger has a old father
His father took sick and overlies
bad in the long term
This younger hoped dad could drink and
happy
But he hasn't money.
The younger worded hard.
One day, he smelt a flavor in mountain.
He went to watch, the waterfall became
liquor.
The younger took liquor and gave his dad
Like this story, you also...
He has slept.
Well, I will give dad a present.
I will buy a present to dad.
Be careful.
Dad.
Doraemon, morning.
What's this?
Dad's present.
Macrobian cole.
You could drink water as you eat cole.
Drink water
Please drink.
I am not a goldfish.
Drink water couldn't make me happy.
It's good usquebaugh.
Coul mix with water, it could become
liquor.
Thank you.
Yes, it is delicious.
You also could drink.
But I am a child.
Oh.
It just is normal water, mama
What? Time is early, you are loud.
Don't care it, come on, mama, have a
drink.
What's wrong? Your face is red.
I have some chore to do.
Yum yum.
If you like, you could drink to
the top of your bent.
My wind is hot more and more.
Rumour said drinking in the morning,
it is better for your health.
Do you think so?
Yes.
It's water.
Don't drink more.
Never mind
it just is water, give it to me.
But if you piss off, it will be bad,
you will be snippy.
I will play with Nobita
Doraemon
Honey.
Yes.
Honey, you have a drink too.
Oh, mama has pissed off like this.
Although it's expensive,
I am willing to do it for dad.
Be careful.
You are saucebox.
Doraemon, that is my gift.
You are Nobita
You go to far, you get away with my gift
No, it isn't fit if I bring out liquor
now
Why
You come here for a moment.
What's wrong?
It's dangerous
Mama, it's dangerous, hurry to come down
What did you say?
I ever studied ballet long long ago.
Papa, bring water to me.
What happened with mama?
Mama, hurry to come down.
Actually...
Nobita
Yes.
Have you gone to school?
You!
You shouldn't do this case
and make us worry.
I should give Doraemon a
lesson on occasion.
This water is weird.
I feel good.
Nobita, what are you doing?
What's matter?
Mama, this water is weird.
Honey.
Mama, what happened?
How ogrish! Gold boa's head.
Nobita
As your retribution, stand outside
classroom
Yes.
I can't bear.
What's wrong?
My feet are powerless
If the kind of machine occurs, if you
use it, your feet won't be powerless.
You haven't done anything when you are
home, why did your feet are powerless?
I have been amerced to stand when I am
school usually, so my feet are pained.
So you should be care,
don't amerce to stand again.
It's difficult...
I am confidence.
I will forget to bring textbook again.
And have a doze.
So I ask you if you have a machine,
my feet won't be powerless if I use it.
Let you be.
What is this?
It is gold boa's head.
It is dangerous weapon, you must
be careful when you use it.
Its eye shoot out light
it will eat living growth's muscle
and make it become stone.
It's dangerous, I don't want it.
Nothing, if you are careful, it will be
good.
Really?
Face its foot, open its lid slowly
I can't move.
Feet...feet can't move.
Shit...
My feet became stone.
Your feet became stone, so you won't
feel tied when you stand for many hours.
You are right.
I won't fear to stand.
If you pull boa's hair
you will resume.
You are right.
I will bring it to school tomorrow.
Nobita, you forgot to bring your textbook
Stand outside classroom.
Yes.
How breezy.
After I have it, I feel I sit on stone.
Well
I could use it to make dislike man
become stone.
No, no, it's boring.
I should make my hand become stone
and beat Gian
he must be dizzy
How happy-
It is good.
You have been punished to stand,
you are also happy
So you stand till you let out.
Yes.
It is late for going back home.
Shit, Gold boa's head.
What? You lost gold boa's head.
It lost at the post-mount of the school
It is troublesome.
When someone close to it, he will
become stone.
We must find it at once.
Around here.
It shouldn't be same place.
This boa knows to raise its speed.
Even its speed is slow like tortoise.
If we find it, how to catch it?
Don't be find by gold boa
Be quiet and close to it, then
use this box lid it fast
I hope we could find it ASAP.
Hush
He is teacher.
Hey...
Became stone.
Don't be careless, it is be around here.
D...Doraemon
It is there.
My foot can't move, Doraemon
Don't leave me alone.
Doraemon has been become stone...
What, it's troublesome.
Yes.
It will be bad if we can't find ASAP.
You help me, all right?
I don't know.
It is Nobita your liability, you should
catch it by yourself.
If we can't catch it soon, it will go
to your house.
It will make me trouble
Nobita, you must engage for it.
It is your fault.
Because you thought this weird idea,
it cause this case.
No.
Leave it to me, I have a good way.
What?
Don't ask more, follow me, you will know
Gian, if you go into home
The gold boa will...
Well, I hide here, you go to find it
and elicit it to here
What?
I don't want.
Nobita...
You don't run before me, I don't want...
Good...
Suneo, jeez, you tumble me, ouch...
Appear
My body hasn't power. Hurry to run...
Nobita you caught it by yourself
How to catch?
It is unimaginable.
Because I let it run away.
So I have this liability.